so i was a late bloomer what do you mean by that i mean i didn't have titties till like 2000
i didn't get my first kiss till prom 10th grade and then i didn't get kissed again until senior
year shout to andre small and then i didn't get kissed again until like the summer uh yeah and
that wasn't for a lack of trying like to i mean shout to marquise price um i mean really what it
was was i was a late bloomer like they they wasn't checking for me i remember sitting down in front
of the library with scott cunningham and him telling me like uh let me holler at you real quick
where was he from orlando okay oh yeah this is all orlando that's at florida and he was like so
check it it's been brought to my attention that you got a little crush on me and though i'm very
flattered uh there are currently activities that i partake in that you don't partake in and i won't
want you to feel pressure to partake in them activities so i just think it would actually
be in both of our best interests you know to just keep it cool that was very gentleman like way of
like putting it together though scott cunningham ladies and gentlemen